Mom !
Nan ! Mom !
What 's wrong , Mom ?
Bon !
Hello , Danai do you know ...
Get out of the house now !
Your sister-in-law is the one !
Bon , don 't die on me !
Art of the Devil
Why ?
What have we done to you ?
Why are you doing this ?
Sign this paper .
No .
Answer my question first !
Actually
it is not about you .
Honestly , I even like you .
Really !
Don 't think about it .
Better luck next time .
At first I just met your Dad and his friends .
He really likes you .
C 'mon , take the job and call him .
What is the number ?
Hold on .
Okay , tell me
09-916 ...
I dare you to take off your clothes and dance .
Are you sure you are pregnant ?
I suspect it because my period is 2 months late .
How do you know it 's mine ?
How can you say that ?
I have only been with you .
If there is a baby , you must do something .
Get this straight ! I won 't be cheated !
Tell me frankly .
How much do you want ?
One million baht .
I thought your dad would let me go .
There is no need to cry over this .
Did I say I would leave you ?
Silly girl .
Who are they ?
For one million baht , you have to be shared .
Help !
Let me go !
Bastards !
Catch her !
Let me go !
And you think he will adopt the baby ?
He gave a lot of money .
Why don 't you get an abortion ?
No !
I want to keep it .
Blow the candle .
You 've got to pay more than one million baht .
Who is this lady ?
Go ahead Dad .
I 'll take care of it here .
Let 's talk outside !
Here !
Stay away from my family !
Get this straight !
You won 't get another dime from me .
You bastard !
Six months later
A tragic accident occurred this evening .
Thawee Thepsoontorn , a property broker , jumped off a bridge .
Police have not determined cause of death .
Murder by witchcraft
Come on , let 's have fun upstairs .
Can we go in your room ?
Sure
Who 's there ?
The whole family of a famous architect was murdered last night .
Shots were reported at midnight at Siwahiran 's house .
Police found the bodies of a man and three females .
Is he in ?
He 's upstairs .
A child , aged 10 , and another unidentified woman .
Police identifies the man as the second son , Amnat .
He had been drinking .
He shot his girl friend , his sister and then himself .
His mother was found dead of a heart attack .
Later Cha-am police found the architect , Pratan , also dead in his beach house .
There were cuts around his head .
Nails were also found near his body .
Donate some coffins to the temple , equal to the number of deaths .
Then the spirits won 't bother you .
When are you expecting ?
Why ?
Just want to welcome the healthy baby , that 's all !
The court today awarded all Pratan 's assets to Kamala , his ex-wife .
After the tragic death of the whole family
the estate has been unclaimed for months .
The estate has been awarded to Kamala , the ex common law wife of Pratan .
Let me clarify this .
My children are entitled to the inheritance .
You know what I think .
Life sucks !
It 's different for you .
You and your mom hit the jackpot ?
Why you ?
Because you are related to that son of a bitch ?
But I am his child .
Who are you ?
Who am I ?
I am the one your father took for a ride , bitch !
You must have led him on .
Shut up ! You must have led him on .
Do you still think you are lucky ?
Enough !
I move into the mansion tomorrow morning .
Okay guys , let 's drink to the nouveau riche !
Cheers !
Sorry .
How are you ?
Brother Ruj !
Sorry , I am not a good drinker .
Don 't run , Bon !
Take it upstairs . Be careful it 's fragile .
Please place this one next to the lamp .
Nan , tell them where to place your things .
Can you manage ?
Why did you drink so much ?
Yes .
Can I call you again ?
Bye .
What a smile .
Was it your girlfriend ?
You will meet her when it is time .
I won 't disappoint you .
OK
Gotcha drunkard !
One body in this room , it was his wife .
Three more were out there .
It was real spooky . I still get Goosebumps .
How was it ?
Do you like the house ?
It is good , Mom .
It is much bigger than expected .
You deserve this .
Your father should have provided before .
I couldn 't myself .
This belongs to all of us , Mom .
Remember telling me about seeing ghosts in your house ?
Do you still see them ?
I don 't know .
I was tipsy at the time .
You look pale .
What happened ?
Maybe I got bewitched .
Don 't joke like that !
You should make merit at the temple to bring luck .
What for ?
C 'mon , we can go this evening .
I 've already made appointment with the master .
You just want someone to go with you .
But no thanks .
I 'm probably imagining things .
What 's with her !
One mistake after another !
Ad !
Is Nan here ?
She is not in yet .
Tell her to see me when she gets in .
Yes .
ASAP , got it ?
Come on out .
Are you going to see your master now ?
I think I 'm really unlucky .
Really ?
Let 's go .
Did you bring pictures ?
Yes , I did .
Come in .
Nanthakan has left this world .
She is being reborn .
May she have a good birth and be rid of bad karma .
Who is that ?
Damn , he will be unlucky !
Are you watching the news ?
Why ?
It is the freak that ate our offering .
Did he get the curse in my place ?
Yes .
One shouldn 't disrespect these things !
It suddenly happens , see ?
You 're not coming , are you ?
I didn 't know Ruj was coming .
Please tell him that it will be my treat next time .
Yes .
Tell him to ask Boom for my Sports Club card too .
Bye for now .
He 's terrible .
I 've asked him many times not to work in that place .
It is full of drunks .
Mom , it 's good that he has a job .
Ajob is a job .
So what if the men drink a little .
Unlike some people that can 't hold it .
Okay , you souse .
Serves him right to miss this nice meal !
Ruj has a girlfriend . I think we 're going to hear good news soon .
Neng and I are grown up . Everything 's going good .
We will take care of you .
Don 't make a face .
It is not good for you .
Okay .
He said not to forget his membership card .
Please ask Boom for it .
Yes , Mom .
You can stop playing .
What 's going on ?
I told him that I want to propose to a beautiful woman out here .
It doesn 't sound very romantic but I do hope she wouldn 't refuse .
Boom , will you marry me ?
Hello .
What 's wrong ?
When are you going to deliver the story ?
Didn 't you get my email ?
Yeah ! I got it .
But it 's different from what I told you to write .
There is evidence on friends of Pratan .
Believe me they were killed by the same black magic as Pratan 's family .
Black magic ! Rubbish !
You 've been a year on this story !
Don 't you write anything else ?
What 's with you ?
Do you want a prize ?
I 'd like to make reservation for a wedding reception .
Please hold I will connect you .
Okay .
May I help you ?
Please hold , there 's a call waiting .
What about the design ?
Everything 's okay .
We are here for the samples
and we will show them to you at the office , okay ?
Okay , come back quick !
Bye .
Would you like to confirm your reservation ? What is your name ?
His name is Ruj Siwahiran , reserved for the 20th of this month .
It is confirmed on the 20th .
Good .
Thank you very much .
Pardon me ...
Are you okay
Clumsy bugger !
Smile !
Don 't you have something to do ?
Go check on the groom .
Then we had better check on the girls .
Bon !
Have you seen my friend ?
What is it , Neng ?
Let 's look inside .
It is the first time I have made a bridal gown .
That is why it doesn 't quite fit .
Good that you look good in anything .
Saves me some work .
Don 't you think so ?
Yes .
Can 't you wait till after the wedding ?
Don 't get her knocked up before the wedding .
Are you nuts ? It was just a kiss .
You never know . I am off .
Are you frightened ?
Of course , you are .
But don 't you want to hear about the others ?
Enough ! I said that 's enough !
Not yet .
You want to hear about them , don 't you ?
Where were we ?
Oh yes , the next body .
So you didn 't send that email on black magic , right ?
No , it must have been a ghost mail .
It doesn 't hurt to believe in this .
The more you know the better .
How is it now ? Do you feel strange ?
What are you girls up to ?
What 's wrong ? You look strange .
Nothing , I 've been in the sun too long .
Don 't be concerned .
Not just his face , his ears too .
Maybe he 's under a spell .
What spell ?
Woon 's spell !
Don 't underestimate them .
We 're joking . Why so uptight ?
Yeah , she 's so tight in that .
We received a black magic email .
What ?
One warns about answering to your name called out .
If you answer the spell will get you .
That 's crazy !
How can you not respond when called ? People will call you a snob .
It 's won 'th a try .
How about a bet ?
How 's that ?
Go through a whole day without answering to anyone .
I dare you .
It 's a bet .
Just don 't loose it .
Let 's go over there .
Neng !
He is dead serious .
He doesn 't even answer his brother .
What 's with him ?
My brother is getting weird .
I 'll just check my office then I 'll meet you in the lobby , okay ?
Okay .
You can 't scare me .
Where have you been ?
I was drawing pictures with my new friend .
Let me see , who 's this ?
Neng ...
Yes ?
What 's wrong ?
Neng ! Neng !
How are you son ?
What did the doctor say ?
An ulcer .
It was really painful . As if someone was twisting it
Told you !
Irregular meals without rest . You asked for an ulcer .
But an ulcer shouldn 't have caused this much pain .
I had one once but I was okay after some medication .
What do you want to eat tomorrow ?
Why ? Will you get it if I tell you ?
Much obliged !
No , just asking .
In case an offering is needed after your death .
Nonsense !
Stop kidding ! You are not kids anymore .
Stay with your brother tonight .
I 'll come back in the morning .
I am going now .
I 'll take you home , Mom .
Bye Mom .
Bye .
Get well soon .
Bye Ruj and Boom
Excuse me .
It is normal .
Eyes are popping out .
I 'll tell Woon .
C 'mon Sis , I 'm not feeling well .
Sis , believe it or not , I have seen weird things too .
Like what ?
Get some sleep . I will go tell them .
Neng !
No !
She is still shocked by his death .
She claims he was smothered by eels .
But his body showed nothing unusual .
Give her time to adjust and she will get better .
Three months later .
I am Danai , a reporter . Here 's my card .
Can I talk to you , in private , about your brother 's death ?
Let 's go .
Your brother didn 't die a natural death .
He was cursed .
You are all in danger .
Someone wants to harm you .
It might be hard to believe , but ...
But if something happens let me know .
Maybe I can help .
How is my house ?
Is it a pool ? No , it is not .
Who would want to swim in this ?
These deaths are very strange and mysterious .
How is my father 's death related to my brother 's death ?
Black magic is involved .
Spells were cast upon your brother too .
I told my editor but he calls it all nonsense .
Have you ever heard of cowhide or nails found inside people ?
The world is a struggle between good and evil , between life and death .
We have good knowledge , and too , have evil knowledge .
These two opposing forces are all around us .
Some of us are lucky , some aren 't .
I once had a bad pain inside .
X-rays showed a cleaver in my stomach .
But nothing was found when they operated .
This is hard to understand .
Your family is facing the same enemy as Pratan .
What has that to do with us ?
It has to do with your father 's estate .
What 's wrong ?
Nan ?
How do you feel ?
I won 't let you die easily .
You shouldn 't have made problems .
Ruj loved you .
I want to do the same .
Do you have asthma attacks often ?
Ever since I was young .
I 'm used to it .
Explain about magic potions ?
Magic potions are poisons placed in food .
The poisons act the next time the same food is eaten .
I want to know if you ever loved anyone .
Did you love my brother at all ?
He was my only love .
Love ? How can you say that ?
You chose him as a victim from beginning !
Darling , I 'm packed .
Would you like me to pack for you too ?
I will pack myself .
Since Neng died , Mom has got worse .
I am so happy that we 're moving back in with her .
What are you doing ?
Ruj , I 'm sorry .
I was afraid that you wouldn 't love me .
I don 't want to be alone .
I didn 't mean to .
I was afraid that you wouldn 't love me .
The dolls ensure that we love each other until the day we die .
I got them because I love you .
Don 't be superstitious !
Dolls or not , I still love you .
Don 't think about it .
Who sold them to you ?
Dolls are used to pacify crying babies .
Let 's throw them away !
Don 't cry .
I will get you some tissue paper .
What 's that ?
You know I don 't drink .
Just a little bit .
We don 't want people to say that my man is not macho .
You 've been acting strange lately .
Is everything okay ?
You can drink only one glass , otherwise our baby will get drunk .
I just want to please you .
I will hold you all night .
Did you hear that , Baby ?
Mommy is going to hold me all night .
Don 't you want to come with me , Sweetheart ?
You know all my friends .
No , I don 't feel well .
Go and enjoy yourself .
See you then .
You lied !
You told me that you loved him and you sent him to die .
I 've warned you not to talk like that .
You don 't know shit .
I didn 't want to do it at all .
Are you drinking water ?
How can you drink a toast with water ?
Have a real drink !
You know that I don 't drink .
Do it for your friends ?
Are you my real friend ?
What do you want ?
Let the game decide , okay ?
Okay .
One of the glasses has alcohol .
If you 're lucky , you pick water .
But if not , then you will have to drink with us all night .
You guys are really something .
If you don 't pick one , I will .
I choose this one .
Okay ?
Okay !
What the ?
Ruj !
Help !
Boom .
Don 't leave me .
It was like this when I saw them .
I dare not remove them .
What 's going on ?
Who 'll be next ?
Me , Mom , or Bon ?
I 'm not afraid ! Whoever it is .
I 'm not scared of anything .
I dare them to face me !
I can 't take it anymore .
I can 't take it anymore !
Take it easy , Nan .
It 's okay .
Take it easy .
You must have felt sad but you know what ?
I felt nothing because I didn 't start all this .
If you need to blame someone , blame your father .
How could you do all those things ?
What is your heart made of ?
How could you kill someone that you loved ?
Stop talking about your brother !
I 'm telling you to stop ! Shut up !
Bitch !
It hurts , doesn 't it ?
But it 's nothing compared to my hurt .
I didn 't want him to die . I just wanted him all to myself .
He was going to be the end of his line and I am his lawful wife .
He shouldn 't have suspected me .
I had no choice but to kill all of you .
Go to bed , Mom .
I have to go now , okay ?
Don 't stay up late .
Draw like this . Color this way .
Not that , it 's not right .
Bon ...
Sister .
Sister , would you like to paint with me ?
What 's wrong , Nan ?
Who were you playing with ?
My friend . She teaches me how to draw .
Here 's Mom , Nan , Bon , and this is my friend .
I will kill you .
You must die .
What 's wrong Mom ?
Mom ! Stop it !
Go get a rope , Nan quick !
Don 't hurt me !
Hurry up , Nan !
Help !
What 's wrong ?
There 's a spirit following you .
But don 't worry she only wants to play .
Where 's she now , your holiness ?
She 's right behind you .
What do you think about your sister-in-law ?
How does she feel about your family ?
Nothing .
She gets along well with all of us , especially Mom .
Mom likes her even more now that Ruj is gone .
It could be that she 's carrying his baby , but why do you ask ?
Nothing . Just making conversation .
After the death of the first and second sons
Kamala started to act strange .
I may be wrong in suspecting that someone close
to the family is behind this .
Do him . He is interfering .
Name of patient : Not found
Mrs. Jittima Siwahiran : Patient 's name not found .
General hospital , good afternoon .
Hello , I 'd like to know when my wife 's next appointment with the doctor is .
Her name is Jittima Siwahiran .
May we have your number ?
02-5133408
I 'll call you back .
Thank you . Goodbye .
Bon !
Come here .
What are you doing here ?
Why are you crying ?
I don 't want to play with her anymore .
Who ?
Who don 't you want to play with ?
She said that we would all die .
I don 't want to play with her .
I 'm here .
You don 't need to be afraid . I won 't let anything happen to any of us .
No one will die .
Damn !
Hello .
I 'm calling from the hospital .
It turns out that there 's no Jittima under our prenatal care .
She was here only for an annual check up .
Are you sure ?
Definitely ! Her check up shows that she can 't have a baby .
Hello . Are you there ? Hello !
Hello ?
I 'm afraid I have bad news .
Frankly , your baby might not be normal .
The ultrasonic shows
that it is deformed .
You must be prepared for this .
Death Certificate
Sister , come and play with me .
What do you want ?
What do you want from me ?
I don 't care who you are !
I 'm not afraid of you !
I want you out of here right now !
Nan !
Mom !
I am in pain ! Please help me !
Bon !
Get out of the house now !
Your sister-in-law is the one !
Bon !
Bon , don 't die on me !
This has gone on too long .
Do as I said if you don 't want to end up like her .
Don 't try to fool me . Stop !
I said stop !
H-Help me !
Who can help you ? The reporter ?
He must be dead by now .
But you , you can 't die yet .
You must sign the paper first .
Sign it !
Do you want to save your mom and your brother ?
Believe me .
Sign it .
Nan ...
How are you ?
Danai , help my mom !
Bon !
Hello .
That reporter is not dead . You know what to do , don 't you ?
Everything is normal except the abdominal cavity .
It 's a big piece of animal hide
The child could have swallowed it .
The surprising thing is , it is getting bigger .
Bon !
Bon , where are you ?
Mom !
Mom , this is me .
Mom , this is me ! Wake up !
Wake up ! Mom !
Mom !
No , Mom !
Mom .
No !
Stop !
You stop !
Bon !
You 're hard to kill .
Let 's see if you can survive this time .
Just my brother and I are left .
Please spare us .
I will give you anything you want .
Please let us go .
When you are dead , everything will be mine .
I am the wife of Ruj .
The estate will be mine .
No way ! It won 't .
Everyone will know that you 're the killer .
Not true !
What I 've done will not be in vain .
My baby and I will inherit the estate .
The estate should have been mine , not yours .
You created all these problems .
Shut up !
Shut up ! Bitch !
Nan .
Nan , help me !
Bon .
Bon , don 't go !
Bon come back here .
Bon !
Bon ! Come back .
Turn around Bon !
Stay still . Come back .
Turn around , Bon !
Bon !
Come back . Do you hear ?
Nan .
Danai once told me that he used this information
in a story called " Art of the Devil " .
He recorded it on this tape .
He was accused of being superstitious but I confirm that this is a true story .
I never believed it was possible until it happened to my family
and Danai .